<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyBlog</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="aboutMe">I am an undergraduate student in Computer Science and Engineering at Varendra University. By this time, I am trying to build up my skills to build up the best career. I am interested in essential learning and experience.
        \n\nAs a Computer Science student, I want to know more about programming languages and solve real-life problems. In the future, I will start a new company to develop software applications.
        \n\nFrom the moment I discovered the world of Android development, I was captivated by the possibilities it offered. The Android platform\'s vast user base and its ability to empower people through mobile applications inspired me to embark on this journey. With a deep appreciation for Kotlin\'s modern and concise syntax, I quickly recognized its potential to streamline my development process and create robust applications.
        \n\nI possess a solid foundation in programming principles and have honed your skills in Kotlin through dedicated self-study and hands-on projects. From variables and control flow to object-oriented concepts and design patterns, I have built a strong understanding of the language, enabling me to write clean and efficient code.
        \n\nWith a strong work ethic, a growth mindset, and an unwavering passion for Android development, I am well on my way to becoming a highly skilled Android application developer using Kotlin. My dedication to mastering my craft and my commitment to delivering exceptional mobile experiences will undoubtedly propel me toward success in the dynamic world of Android app development.
    </string>
    <string name="contactMe">
        \nContact with me:
        \nGmail : mdshariarhossainsun01822@gmail.com
        \nFacebook: https://www.facebook.com/sun01822
        \nMobile No: +8801521505130
        \n\n</string>
</resources>